Hello friends, my name is Vinay and you guys are
watching Vinay Tech.  So today I am going to
tell you about ICICI LBD
Quarter 4 Result.  So how was the quarter
four result of ICICI LBR, I am going to
tell you in full detail.  So let's
start.  So you guys can see
here is a notification from ICC LBD.
This notification came on April 15, 2025
and in this notification, the dividend and the
result of quarter 4 have been announced.
So let's see in detail.  So
here the dividend that you are going to get will be given as per
seven for equity shares.  That
means if you have one share
then you will get ₹7 from ICICI LBR.
So this was about dividend
and no record date has been announced yet.
When the announcement is made, I will
tell you all in detail.  So let's
look at the quarter four results now.  So you
guys can see that here is the
statement of audited financial
result from ICCI lumber for quarter and year end, the
result is till 31 March 2025 and whatever
calculation is done in lakhs, 3 months
year end year end total income in current quarter
588000 117 in previous quarter
588283 and in previous year 5 1653 there is
decrement on quarterly basis and there
is improvement on year on year basis in total
income total expenses how much is the company spending,
in current quarter 5 lakh
43525 in previous quarter 59747 and
in the quarter before that 46380 quarter on quarterly
basis expenses have increased and on
year on year basis also expenses have increased
and under writing profit and loss
in current quarter
2096 in previous quarter 15230 and
in the quarter before that
2355 quarter on quarter  There
is increment on base pay and there is also decrement on year on year basis.
Operating profit and loss
in the current quarter is
41592, in the previous quarter is 68536 and
in the quarter before that is 56158. There is a quarterly
basis pay decrement and there is also a year-on-year
basis pay decrement. In operating
profit and loss, total
expenses and non-operating results, you
can see that total expenses
in the current quarter are 731, in the previous quarter is 140
and in the quarter before that is 9749. There is a
quarterly basis pay increment and there is a year-
on-year basis pay increment. Profit
and loss before tax is 66820,
in the previous quarter is 961 and in the quarter before that is
697.779. There is a quarterly basis pay
decrement and there is also a year-on-year basis pay
decrement. In profit and loss before
tax and profit and loss after tax is
5959, in the previous quarter is 72438 and
in the quarter before that is 51950. There is a quarterly
basis pay decrement and there is a year-on-year basis.  There is
also decrement in profit and
loss after tax and EPS earnings per
share in current quarter 10.29,
in previous quarter 14.63 and in the quarter before that
10.55, there is decrement on quarter on quarter basis
and there is also decrement in EPS on year basis,
so this was quarter
three, so this was quarter four result of
ICICI LBR, so if this video is useful for you,
please do like, share, comment and
subscribe to my channel Bina Tech.